[{"question":" Teams may encounter the need for \"technical\" user stories. Who decides the priority of these?","options":[{"text":"the Product Owner with help from Operations","correct":false},{"text":"the Tech Lead with help from the Product Owner","correct":false},{"text":"the Product Owner with help from the Tech Lead","correct":true},{"text":"the Tech Lead with help from Operations","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":" What is the Scrum Master's role during the daily stand-up?","options":[{"text":"Congratulate the team on their great work.","correct":false},{"text":"Stand outside the circle of developers and listen for impediments.","correct":true},{"text":"The Scrum Master should not attend—this meeting is for developers only.","correct":false},{"text":"Ask each developer what they did since the last daily standup.","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":" Which factor should not be considered during Sprint Planning?","options":[{"text":"the team's velocity","correct":false},{"text":"the number of stories in the product backlog","correct":true},{"text":"the stories that are ready","correct":false},{"text":"the team's capacity","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":" A team member has been showing signs of great personal distress: crying at work, snapping at colleagues, having heated phone conversations. As Team Facilitator, what should you do?","options":[{"text":"Give the team member space and time to deal with their personal issues.","correct":false},{"text":"Tell the others on the team that their teammate needs some emotional support.","correct":false},{"text":"Notify the team member's manager of your observations and ask the manager for help.","correct":true},{"text":"Ask the team member if they would like to talk about what might be going on with them personally.","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":" Which statement describes the flow of work in the Scaled Agile Framework?","options":[{"text":"It is a \"push\" system.","correct":false},{"text":"It is \"push\" at the top and \"pull\" at the bottom.","correct":false},{"text":"It is a \"pull\" system.","correct":false},{"text":"It is neither \"push\" nor \"pull.\"","correct":true}],"illustrator":""},{"question":" What is the Product Owner's role in deciding the priority of work in the sprint backlog?","options":[{"text":"None—the Scrum Master should prioritize the work in the sprint backlog.","correct":false},{"text":"The PO should prioritize the items in the sprint backlog.","correct":false},{"text":"The developers prioritize work unless they cannot complete it, in which case the PO should prioritize the remaining work.","correct":false},{"text":"None—the developers should prioritize the work in the sprint backlog.","correct":true}],"illustrator":""},{"question":" The Scaled Agile Framework advocates that, if you measure only one thing, what should you measure?","options":[{"text":"quality","correct":false},{"text":"predictability of delivery","correct":false},{"text":"cost of delay","correct":true},{"text":"return on investment","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":" Why should you apply Weighted Shortest Job First?","options":[{"text":"to maximize the return on investment","correct":false},{"text":"to determine the economic sequencing of the backlog","correct":true},{"text":"to visualize queue length","correct":false},{"text":"to fulfill a commitment to quality","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":" You have classified the features in your backlog according to risk and value. Which features should the development team work on first?","options":[{"text":"low-value and high-risk","correct":false},{"text":"high-value and high-risk","correct":true},{"text":"high-value and low-risk","correct":false},{"text":"low-value and low-risk","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". In the Scaled Agile Framework, what is the role of Enablers?","options":[{"text":"They help extend the Architectural Runway.","correct":true},{"text":"They connect vision to mission so the organization can be successful.","correct":false},{"text":"They support team building.","correct":false},{"text":"They remove the impediments to quality.","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". Which outcome is not expected of a Sprint Review?","options":[{"text":"The team demonstrates its completed work.","correct":false},{"text":"The team reflects on how to improve its performance.","correct":true},{"text":"Items in the backlog may be reprioritized.","correct":false},{"text":"Stakeholders give feedback about the work completed.","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". What is not a technique used for splitting user stories?","options":[{"text":"split by line-of-business","correct":false},{"text":"split compound user stories","correct":true},{"text":"split by alternative paths","correct":false},{"text":"split by interface","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". Who decides what the team will work on?","options":[{"text":"the Scrum Master","correct":false},{"text":"a self-organizing team","correct":true},{"text":"the Product Owner","correct":false},{"text":"the Product Manager","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". Which choice is not a Scrum value?","options":[{"text":"focus","correct":false},{"text":"integrity","correct":true},{"text":"courage","correct":false},{"text":"commitment","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". What should happen if the Product Owner does not accept a story by the end of the iteration?","options":[{"text":"The team does not get credit for the story's points in its velocity calculation.","correct":false},{"text":"The story should be sliced to reflect the work completed.","correct":false},{"text":"The acceptance criteria should be adjusted to reflect the work completed.","correct":false},{"text":"The story should be shown to stakeholders for their feedback.","correct":true}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". Which statement is not true about the product backlog?","options":[{"text":"It is a list of work items that are behind schedule.","correct":true},{"text":"The items are maintained in priority order.","correct":false},{"text":"Anyone on the team can propose an item for it.","correct":false},{"text":"It includes all of the work to be done.","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". A project has some major risks that the team wants to mitigate. What is the best way to monitor how well this effort is going?","options":[{"text":"risk-based spike","correct":false},{"text":"risk-adjusted backlog","correct":false},{"text":"risk velocity chart","correct":false},{"text":"risk burndown graph","correct":true}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". The VP of engineering wants to start a Team Member of the Sprint Award to recognize a top performer in each group. What would you advise the VP?","options":[{"text":"This is not a good idea unless there has been recent employee feedback that people feel underappreciated.","correct":false},{"text":"It is a good idea as long as a different person is recognized in each sprint.","correct":false},{"text":"It is a good idea because awards can motivate people to do their best.","correct":false},{"text":"This is not a good idea because it can destroy the team unity that is essential to achieving high performance.","correct":true}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". What is a difference between a team's task board and a Kanban?","options":[{"text":"A Kanban has an explicit rule to limit WIP. (explicit rule applies to scrum team's task board: tasks cannot be added to the scrum board in the middle of a sprint)","correct":true},{"text":"A Kanban shows the backlog of work.","correct":false},{"text":"A Kanban does not use a Definition of Done.","correct":false},{"text":"A Kanban shows the status of the work items.","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". The team complains that \"things have been falling through the cracks lately.\" What should you do?","options":[{"text":"Ask the team's manager to make role assignments so the team can catch up.","correct":false},{"text":"Conduct a workshop to identify all of the things that need to be done and see who can help with each.","correct":true},{"text":"Refer to the team's RACI (Responsible, Accountable, Consulted, Informed) assignments.","correct":false},{"text":"Meet with the Tech Lead and Product Owner to try to identify what can be done.","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". In Large-Scale Scrum, what is the recommended ratio of Scrum Masters to teams?","options":[{"text":"One Scrum Master can support up to five teams.","correct":false},{"text":"Large teams should have two Scrum Masters.","correct":false},{"text":"There should be one Scrum Master per team.","correct":false},{"text":"One Scrum Master can support one to three teams.","correct":true}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". In the Cynefin framework, where are \"best practices\" most appropriate?","options":[{"text":"in the Complex regime","correct":false},{"text":"in the Complicated regime","correct":false},{"text":"in the Chaotic regime","correct":false},{"text":"in the Obvious regime","correct":true}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". A manager informs you that a developer from another team is between assignments, and she wants to place the developer on your team for a few sprints. What should you do?","options":[{"text":"Explain to the manager that this will be disruptive to the team and ask that another assignment be found.","correct":true},{"text":"Explain the situation to the team and ask them to go with the flow.","correct":false},{"text":"Explain the situation to your manager and ask them to resolve it.","correct":false},{"text":"When the temporary developer shows up, assign them to write documentation.","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". The Product Owner complains to you that the team is not working hard enough and they need to increase their velocity by at least 50%. Which action should you not take?","options":[{"text":"Share the feedback from the PO and challenge the team to increase their velocity.","correct":true},{"text":"Ask the PO to explain the business context to the team.","correct":false},{"text":"Explain the impact of technical debt to the PO and the benefits of devoting some capacity to reducing it.","correct":false},{"text":"Hold a Value Stream Mapping workshop to identify and reduce waste.","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". What is the name of the practice in which a cross-functional team collaborates intensively to develop a new product idea?","options":[{"text":"Hackathon","correct":true},{"text":"Scrum at Scale","correct":false},{"text":"Innovation and Planning","correct":false},{"text":"Magnum Focus","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". The team's manager wants to attend the Sprint Retrospective. What should you do?","options":[{"text":"Agree to the manager's request and notify the team.","correct":false},{"text":"Propose that the manager attend only every other retrospective.","correct":false},{"text":"Propose a different forum for the manager to meet with the team.","correct":true},{"text":"Ask the team if it is okay with them that the manager attend.","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". Who is responsible for a Scrum team's performance?","options":[{"text":"the team","correct":true},{"text":"the Scrum Master","correct":false},{"text":"the Product Owner","correct":false},{"text":"the Engineering Manager","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". Which statement concerning small, frequent releases of software is true?","options":[{"text":"The chance for rollback is high.","correct":false},{"text":"It typically requires a high degree of automation.","correct":true},{"text":"The administrative costs are high.","correct":false},{"text":"Backward compatibility may be jeopardized.","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". What is the activity of clarifying and expanding user stories called?","options":[{"text":"story point estimating","correct":false},{"text":"Definition of Done","correct":false},{"text":"user story expansion","correct":false},{"text":"backlog refinement","correct":true}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". Which strategy is preferred for development teams?","options":[{"text":"Optimize for most work done.","correct":false},{"text":"Maximize output and maximize outcome.","correct":true},{"text":"Maximize outcome while minimizing output.","correct":false},{"text":"Optimize for resource utilization.","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". Which statement is true about the actor in a user story?","options":[{"text":"The actor does not have to be a specified role in the solution.","correct":false},{"text":"There must be multiple personas for each actor.","correct":false},{"text":"The actor can be the system itself.","correct":true},{"text":"The system cannot be the actor.","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". Which statement is true about Agile?","options":[{"text":"Agile requires a high degree of up-front planning.","correct":false},{"text":"Once the requirements are agreed to, the team can complete work.","correct":false},{"text":"Agile requires a high degree of discipline.","correct":true},{"text":"Agile works best when there is no contract.","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". Which statement about burndown and burnup charts is not true?","options":[{"text":"Burndown charts show the work remaining to be done.","correct":false},{"text":"Burnup charts show the work completed.","correct":false},{"text":"Burndown charts are more useful than burnup charts.","correct":true},{"text":"Agile project management tools can produce these automatically.","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". What is the name for the practice of going to see a process in use at the point of value delivery?","options":[{"text":"Six Sigma","correct":false},{"text":"Gemba walk","correct":true},{"text":"Total Quality Management","correct":false},{"text":"Kaizen","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". When the team needs to make a decision, what is the best course of action?","options":[{"text":"Try to achieve concensus.","correct":true},{"text":"Take a vote and the majority rules.","correct":false},{"text":"Identify the person who is most knowledgeable and ask them to decide.","correct":false},{"text":"Let the most senior member of the team decide.","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". Which action is something the Team Facillitator should NOT do?","options":[{"text":"Embrace servant leadership.","correct":false},{"text":"Estimate story points.","correct":true},{"text":"Celebrate successes.","correct":false},{"text":"Remove impediments","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". A team needs to do research, design, prototyping. What is this type of story called?","options":[{"text":"Exploratory spike","correct":true},{"text":"Backlog refinement","correct":false},{"text":"Functional decomposition","correct":false},{"text":"R&D","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". Which statement about technical debt is true?","options":[{"text":"Technical debt is another name for bugs","correct":false},{"text":"It is at the Product Owner's description to allocate effort to reduce technical debt.","correct":false},{"text":"Adding technical debt should be avoided at all costs.","correct":true},{"text":"Technical debt is what the Product Owner owes to the developers if they work a lot of overtime to complete the sprint.","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". Which statement about estimating is not true?","options":[{"text":"Absolute estimating is more reliable than relative estimating.","correct":false},{"text":"Relative estimating is more reliable than absolute estimating.","correct":false},{"text":"In estimating, accuracy is more important than precision.","correct":true},{"text":"In estimating, the effort is more important than the time required.","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". Which ceremony should the Product Owner not attend?","options":[{"text":"daily stand-ups","correct":false},{"text":"Sprint Retrospectives","correct":false},{"text":"story point estimating","correct":false},{"text":"code reviews","correct":true}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". Which task is not the Product Owners responsibility?","options":[{"text":"estimating story points","correct":false},{"text":"refining acceptance criteria","correct":false},{"text":"giving feedback to developers about the user stories","correct":true},{"text":"demonstrating the work to stakeholders","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". Which choice is `_not_` considered during Sprint Planning?","options":[{"text":"stories that meet the Definition of Done","correct":true},{"text":"team velocity","correct":false},{"text":"stories that meet the Definition of Ready","correct":false},{"text":"team capacity","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". You have noticed a pattern that the most interesting stories on the Sprint Backlog get started right away, and the least interesting stories languish or don't get done. What should you do?","options":[{"text":"Use a lottery system assign each story.","correct":false},{"text":"Share your observation with the team and invite them to own and solve the problem.","correct":false},{"text":"During story point estimation increase the points assigned to the least interesting stories so the team can boost their velocity.","correct":false},{"text":"Ask the Tech Lead to assign every story to a developer so they all get done efficiently and with accountability.","correct":true}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". What Agile practice best supports this principle: \"At regular intervals, the team reflects on how to become more effective, then tunes and adjusts its behavior accordingly\"?","options":[{"text":"Sprint Review","correct":false},{"text":"Sprint Retrospective","correct":true},{"text":"daily stand-up","correct":false},{"text":"Sprint Demo","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". On what are personas typically based?","options":[{"text":"a sponsors or team members' personalities and traits","correct":false},{"text":"what the developers think is user friendly","correct":false},{"text":"real people, archetypal users, or composites of multiple users","correct":true},{"text":"descriptions of the product's functionality and use","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". Which statement describes Shu Ha Ri?","options":[{"text":"It is a library of coding patterns.","correct":false},{"text":"It is a software testing strategy.","correct":false},{"text":"It is a standard for interface design.","correct":false},{"text":"It is a model for skill development and mastery.","correct":true}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". What does the Agile Manifesto indicate?","options":[{"text":"Responding to change is more valuable than following a plan.","correct":true},{"text":"Documenting requirements up front is more valuable than at the end.","correct":false},{"text":"Following the plan is essential for not going over budget.","correct":false},{"text":"Contract negotiation should be used to settle disputes.","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". What is the main benefit of a working agreement?","options":[{"text":"It specifies core working hours.","correct":false},{"text":"It clarifies the reporting relationships on the team.","correct":false},{"text":"It defines the culture that the team aspires to achieve.","correct":true},{"text":"It compiles everyone's information.","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". What is the name of the information radiator that has multiple columns used to visualize the flow of work?","options":[{"text":"Work Flow Indicator","correct":false},{"text":"Value Stream Map","correct":false},{"text":"Story Map","correct":false},{"text":"Kanban Board","correct":true}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". Which is the best definition of story points?","options":[{"text":"They are a relative measure of the effort needed to complete a story.","correct":true},{"text":"They a measure of development time only, test time is considered separately.","correct":false},{"text":"They are a relative measure of the value of a story.","correct":false},{"text":"They are a measure of time to complete a story.","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". What is a Scrum of Scrums?","options":[{"text":"It is technique for two or more teams working together coordinate their efforts.","correct":true},{"text":"It is another name for the Scrum Master Community of Practice.","correct":false},{"text":"It is an information radiator used to compare the velocity of several teams.","correct":false},{"text":"It is the system demo for teams on the same release train.","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". What is the Product Owner's role regarding the product backlog?","options":[{"text":"The PO must identify the intended users of the features on the backlog.","correct":false},{"text":"The PO is responsible for estimating the size of the total.","correct":false},{"text":"The PO must identify the dependencies that impact the backlog.","correct":true},{"text":"The PO decides what to include in the backlog and what to exclude.","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". Why should a team do refactoring?","options":[{"text":"It assigns developers to other teams in order to eliminate personality conflicts.","correct":false},{"text":"It improves the functionality of the product,","correct":false},{"text":"It recalibrates the success criteria for the product in the marketplace.","correct":false},{"text":"It improves the design, which can lead improved development efficiency and maintainability.","correct":true}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". Which choice is not a benefit generally associated with product demonstrations?","options":[{"text":"Learn about new requirements.","correct":false},{"text":"Learn feature suitability.","correct":false},{"text":"Learn about feature usability.","correct":false},{"text":"Learn about feature estimates.","correct":true}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". What is an information radiator?","options":[{"text":"a list of KPIs for the team","correct":false},{"text":"a list of overdue action items","correct":false},{"text":"the task board","correct":true},{"text":"a highly visible display of key performance data","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". According to the Agile Manifesto, your highest priority is to `**\\_\\_**`.","options":[{"text":"minimize change requests","correct":false},{"text":"satisfy the customer","correct":true},{"text":"get the job done on time","correct":false},{"text":"achieve the desired ROI","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". Product development organizations sometimes use descriptions of archetypal users and their values so that developers can design the system to meet their needs and wants. What are these descriptions called?","options":[{"text":"actors","correct":false},{"text":"roles","correct":false},{"text":"agents","correct":false},{"text":"personas","correct":true}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". The Product Owner is focused on testing a new system concept in the marketplace as quickly and inexpensively as possible. What is this first-generation product called?","options":[{"text":"preproduction version","correct":false},{"text":"focus group demonstrator","correct":false},{"text":"Generation 1 product","correct":false},{"text":"minimum viable product","correct":true}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". To whom should the Product Owner report?","options":[{"text":"the Quality Manager","correct":false},{"text":"the Product Manager","correct":true},{"text":"the Scrum Master","correct":false},{"text":"the Engineering Manager","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". What happens in Sprint 0?","options":[{"text":"The team delivers no story points in that sprint.","correct":false},{"text":"The team does regression testing prior to release to production.","correct":false},{"text":"The team prepares to work on the product backlog.","correct":true},{"text":"This is the time to inspect and adapt.","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". What does the Definition of Done mean?","options":[{"text":"The story meets the INVEST criteria.","correct":false},{"text":"The team has completed all of the work in its Sprint.","correct":false},{"text":"The story has been handed off to the DevOps team.","correct":false},{"text":"The team has agreed on the criteria for story completion.","correct":true}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". Which element is most important when describing your product?","options":[{"text":"its cost","correct":false},{"text":"its licensing terms and conditions","correct":false},{"text":"its benefits","correct":true},{"text":"its features","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". Which choice best describes the Team Facilitator?","options":[{"text":"a meeting scheduler","correct":false},{"text":"a record keeper","correct":false},{"text":"a project manager","correct":false},{"text":"an Agile coach","correct":true}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". What is the name of the technique that divides a story into smaller pieces?","options":[{"text":"mitosis","correct":false},{"text":"story slicing","correct":false},{"text":"disaggregation","correct":true},{"text":"Divide and Conquer","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". A team member comes to you with a complaint about another team member. What should you do?","options":[{"text":"Bring the complaint to the other person and try to resolve the issue.","correct":false},{"text":"Ask them to talk to the other person and try to work it.","correct":false},{"text":"Notify HR of the problem and ask them to handle it.","correct":false},{"text":"Invite both people a meeting and try mediate the conflict.","correct":true}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". What is the forming-storming-norming, performing model of team development known as?","options":[{"text":"the Tuckman model","correct":true},{"text":"the Standard Team model","correct":false},{"text":"Moore's Team Framework","correct":false},{"text":"the Siebert model","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". What is the name of the ceremony in which you inspect the work completed during the sprint?","options":[{"text":"Sprint Retrospective (reflect on the previous sprint, discuss what’s working well, what could be improved, and how to improve it to be more productive)","correct":false},{"text":"Sprint Review (discuss what has been accomplished during the sprint and whether the sprint goal has been met)","correct":true},{"text":"Next-Sprint Planning","correct":false},{"text":"Velocity Confirmation","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". Which choice best describes an Agile Release Train (ART)?","options":[{"text":"continuous delivery","correct":true},{"text":"comprised of the teams within a program","correct":false},{"text":"DevOps Center of Excellence","correct":false},{"text":"Scrum of Scrums","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". As an Agile coach, what should be your attitude toward your team members individual goals and motivations?","options":[{"text":"Understand them—try align personal motivations with the team's progress toward the project goals.","correct":false},{"text":"Nurture them-goals are the reason why people want to be at work.","correct":false},{"text":"Disregard them—personal views have no bearing on reaching the project goals.","correct":false},{"text":"Leverage them—use personal goals encourage team members raise their performance levels.","correct":true}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". Which phrase best describes an Agile team?","options":[{"text":"self-directed","correct":false},{"text":"self-managed","correct":false},{"text":"self-sustaining","correct":false},{"text":"self-organizing","correct":true}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". Which technique does not help prioritize the backlog?","options":[{"text":"MoSCow","correct":false},{"text":"Kano","correct":false},{"text":"WSJF","correct":false},{"text":"Kaizen","correct":true}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". What does the Definition of Ready mean?","options":[{"text":"The story has been tested end is ready for release to production.","correct":false},{"text":"The story is ready to be brought into a sprint.","correct":true},{"text":"The stakeholders are ready to discuss their requirements for story.","correct":false},{"text":"The team has completed sprint 0 and is ready to work.","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". Which is NOT a principle of the Scaled Agile Framework?","options":[{"text":"Centralize decision-making","correct":false},{"text":"Apply systems thinking","correct":false},{"text":"Take an economic view","correct":false},{"text":"Unlock the intrinsic motivation of knowledge workers","correct":true}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". Which statement concerning small, frequent releases of software is true?","options":[{"text":"The chance for rollback is high","correct":false},{"text":"It typically requires a high degree of automation","correct":true},{"text":"Backward compatibility may be jeopardized","correct":false},{"text":"The administrative costs are high","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". What is the definition of capacity?","options":[{"text":"It is an inventory of the team's knowledge and skills that is used to plan the work that they do.","correct":false},{"text":"It is the number of teams that a Team Facilitator can support concurrently.","correct":false},{"text":"It is an adjustment to velocity, used in Spring Planning, to account for reduced availability of team members during the upcoming sprint.","correct":false},{"text":"It is the maximum number of stories that will be allowed in a sprint.","correct":true}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". Which action is something the Team Facilitator should not do?","options":[{"text":"Celebrate Success.","correct":false},{"text":"Embrace servant leadership.","correct":false},{"text":"Remove impediments","correct":false},{"text":"Estimate story points.","correct":true}],"illustrator":""}]